afloral.com 2018-10-30

# Privacy Policy – Afloral.com

Afloral.com Privacy Policy

\-----

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.afloral.com (the “Site”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”.

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:  
\- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.  
\- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.  
\- “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, PayPal account information, and/or Amazon Pay account information), email address, phone number, and EIN/Tax ID number. We refer to this information as “Order Information”.

 ”Personal Information” for the purposes of this Privacy Policy means information that can be used to personally identify you or is associated with any such information, or personal information may be defined by the laws of the location where you live.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:  
\- Communicate with you;  
\- Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and  
\- When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).  IP addresses are not used by us to personally identify individuals, and we does not link IP addresses to other forms of identifiable information, however IP addresses may be considered to be Personal Information under the laws of certain jurisdictions.

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, but not limited to, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site -- you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING  
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by using the links below:  
\- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads  
\- Google: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous  
\- Bing: https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads  
\- Criteo: https://www.criteo.com/privacy/

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.

COOKIE POLICY  
We use cookies from time to time to help personalize your online experience with us. Cookies provide us with information about your use of the site that can help us improve the site and your experience with it. Any personal information collected about you through cookies, as described above, will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you should receive a warning message with each cookie. You may refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser, however you should be aware that our site like most other popular sites may not work well with cookies disabled.  Please be advised that we do not have access to or control over the third party cookies used on the Site.

DO NOT TRACK  
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.  We do not track our visitors across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore we do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals.  However, some third party sites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you.  If you are visiting such sites, your internet browser may allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked.

YOUR RIGHTS  
We do our best to keep your data accurate and up to date, to the extent that you provide us with the information we need to do that.  If your data changes (like a new email address), then you are responsible for notifying us of those changes.  If you would like to find out what Personal Information we have about you, change/correct your data, or have your information removed from our database please email info@afloral.com and we will provide an individual access to any personal information we hold about them within 30 days of a request for that information.  Unless it’s prohibited by law, we’ll remove any personal information about an individual from our servers at their request.  There is no charge for an individual to access or update his or her personal information.  
Your personal information may be collected, stored and/or processed or otherwise used by us or on our behalf inside the United States by third party service providers, to perform cloud storage, payment processing, digital advertising and related functions on our behalf.  As a result, U.S. court, government or law enforcement agencies could obtain disclosure of such information under U.S. law.  By using our Site and services, you understand and consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information to our facilities in the United States and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Policy.  
DATA PRIVACY RIGHTS FOR INDIVIDUALS IN THE EUROPEAN UNION AND/OR THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA   
In addition to your right to certain information contained in this Privacy Policy, pursuant to the General Data Protection Regulation, you have the following rights regarding your personal data that we hold:  
be informed of our intent to transfer your personal information to another country or international organization, the recipients of that information, and where information regarding the applicable privacy safeguards may be obtained;   
request access to your personal information;  
request correction of your personal information if it is incorrect;  
request that we delete or stop processing your personal information under certain circumstances;  
object to our processing of your personal information under certain circumstances;  
request that we restrict our processing of your personal information, and where our processing is based on your consent, withdraw that consent (which may be done by emailing: info@afloral.com without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal;  
request that we transmit your personal information either to you or another service provider under certain circumstances (costs may apply);  
be informed of your right to complain to a supervisory authority if you feel that we have not complied with applicable laws regulating your personal information (contact information for supervisory authorities may be found at:  http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm) 

Please note that the above rights are not absolute, and we may be entitled to refuse requests where exceptions apply.  For more information, or to make a request, please email: info@afloral.com with your name, email address, request, and basis for your request.

DATA RETENTION  
We will retain your Personal Information for as long as your Site account is active or as long as needed to provide you services that you have requested.  We may also retain and use your information in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent abuse, and enforce our agreements.  We do not intend to retain personal information longer than necessary for such purpose(s), unless necessary for compliance with a legal obligation, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.  
SOCIAL MEDIA PLATFORMS AND OTHER WEBSITES  
Our Site includes social media features, like links to our Facebook and Instagram pages. These features may collect information about your IP address and which page you’re visiting on our site, and they may set a cookie to make sure the feature functions properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. We also maintain presences on social media platforms like Facebook, Instagram and Pintrest. Any information, communications, or materials you submit to us via a social media platform is done at your own risk without any expectation of privacy. We cannot control the actions of other users of these platforms or the actions of the platforms themselves. Your interactions with those features and platforms are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

CHILDREN’S INFORMATION  
We do not knowingly collect information from children and do not target or direct this Site to children. The meaning of “children” is subject to the laws and regulations in the jurisdiction in which you are located.  We reserve the right to delete any information we believe to be in violation of this Privacy Policy.

SECURITY  
We take reasonable efforts to protect your personal information.  However, no data transmission over the internet, wireless transmission, or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  Please note that we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and you use our services and provide us with your information at your own risk.  If a security breach causes an unauthorized intrusion into our system that materially affects you, then we will notify you as soon as possible in accordance with applicable legal requirements.

NO LIABILITY  
You understand that electronic communications may be accessed by unauthorized parties when communicated across the internet, network communications facilities, or other electronic means.  You agree that we are not responsible for any electronic communication and/or any of your data which may be lost, altered, intercepted or stored without authorization during the transmission of any data whatsoever across networks not owned and/or operated by us.  We do not guarantee that your information will not be misused or disclosed to third parties.  We will not have any liability to you for any such misuse or disclosure.

CHANGES  
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, without notice to you and in accordance with applicable law, in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. It is your responsibility to check this page periodically for changes.

CONSENT  
By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.  Except as required or allowed by law, we will not use or disclose your Personal Information for any purpose for which you refuse us consent or later withdraw your consent. If you withdraw consent, you agree that in spite of this withdrawal we may continue to use the Personal Information previously provided to us to the extent that we are legally or contractually obligated to do so and to the extent necessary to enforce any contractual obligations you may have to us. You also understand that although you can use our Site for some purposes without providing us with any Personal Information, we need Personal Information about you for some services. If you refuse to provide us with the information we require or later withdraw your consent to use and disclose this information, we may no longer be able to provide you with these services.

CONTACT US  
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by email at info@afloral.com or by mail using the details provided below:

Afloral.com  
Privacy Compliance Officer  
106 East 2nd Street   
Jamestown New York 14701  
USA
